{"data":[{"question":"Is this car capable ________ us all way to our hometown?","a":"in getting","b":"about getting","c":"of getting","d":"for getting","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be capable of doing sth: having the qualities or ability needed to do something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The people at the party were worried about Jane because no one was aware ________ she had gone.","a":"of where","b":"of the place where","c":"where that","d":"the place","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To be aware of: if you are aware that a situation exists, you realize or know that it exists.\u00a0\n- where: used as an adverb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Peter\u00a0did not do well in the class because ________.","a":"he studied bad.","b":"he was not good studywise.","c":"he was a badly student.","d":"he failed to study properly.","answer":"4","explain":"- The reason why Peter did not do well in the class","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"He made a speech at a wedding reception. He spoke during the ________.","a":"wedding","b":"marriage","c":"ceremony","d":"party","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Party: an event at which people meet to celebrate something or to have fun by eating and drinking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Let's ask our teacher how to solve this problem ________ we can't agree on the answer.","a":"because of","b":"since","c":"consequently","d":"as long as","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Since = because.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr.Edward will substitute ________ the history teacher who is out of town.","a":"from","b":"at","c":"for","d":"with","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Substitute something for something: to use something new or different instead of something else.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"________ you select reverse gear, the car goes backwards.","a":"In spite of","b":"Unless","c":"If","d":"For","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"________ I get angry and upset, I try to take ten deep breaths.","a":"Until","b":"Whenever","c":"Therefore","d":"For","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Whenever: as a conjunction (connecting two clauses or phrases)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"A ________ railway accident happened 3 days ago.","a":"fearful","b":"fearfulness","c":"fearless","d":"fearlessness","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A\/an + Noun\/noun phrase (= adj + noun) \n+ Fearful: frightened that something might happen.\u00a0\n+ Fearless: not afraid of anything.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"A small fish needs camouflage to hide itself ________ its enemies cannot find it.","a":"so that","b":"so","c":"therefore","d":"due to","answer":"1","explain":"\n- So that: in order to make something happen, make something possible.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}